{"data":[{"question":"Someone _________ calling for you at the door.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"will be","d":"is being","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The indefinite pronouns anyone, everyone, someone, no one, nobody are always singular and, therefore, require singular verbs \n- Present continuous tense:express the idea that something is happening now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"No one except the two brothers ___ the secret.","a":"knows","b":"know","c":"are knowing","d":"is knowing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Subject (the two brother) is plural\n- Simple present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"Class Six _________ reciting the text now.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"are being","d":"has been","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Subject (class six) is singular \n- Simple present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"___ of the money ___ used up.","a":"One-seconds, have been","b":"One-two, are","c":"One-second, is","d":"One-seconds, has been","answer":"4","explain":"\n- One-seconds= 1\/2\n- Use a singular verb with sums of money or periods of time","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"The number of the people who ___ by bus ___ increasing.","a":"goes, is","b":"goes, are","c":"go, are","d":"go, is","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sometimes the pronoun who, that, or which is the subject of a verb in the middle of the sentence. The pronouns who, that, and which become singular or plural according to the noun directly in front of them \n- The expression the number is followed by a singular verb while the expression a number is followed by a plural verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"All but one ___ here just now.","a":"was","b":"is","c":"were","d":"has been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Subject (all) is plural \n- Simple past tense ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"Many students ___ the same kind of mistake before.","a":"have made","b":"had made","c":"has been made","d":"has made","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense:We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"Kelly, perhaps Doris, _________ playing with her pet cat.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"seems","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject (Kelly or Doris) is singular\n- Present continuous tense\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"Laying eggs ___ the ant queen's full-time job.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"seems","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject (Laying eggs) is singular \n- Simple present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"The art works _________ in 1990.","a":"were set up","b":"were built","c":"was set up","d":"were put up","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Subject (The art works) is singular\n- Simple past + passive voice\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"}]}